uncorneredmarket.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy Policy - Uncornered Market

Uncornered Market found at https://uncorneredmarket.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it and your personal data. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know what personally identifiable information we may collect on the Website and how it may be used. This Privacy Policy only applies to this Website. 

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED?

**Information You Submit Voluntarily:** We may collect personal information from you such as your name, email address, or website URL for certain types of forms or services. For example, you may voluntarily submit your personal information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or filling out a contact form. This information allows us to add your comment, add your email address to the newsletter list, or respond to your contact form message.

**Information We Collect from Others:** We may receive information about you from other website and sources. You may link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile. If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile, we may in some instances receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account. 

**Automatically-Collected Information:** We automatically collect information about you and the device with which you access and use the Website. For example, when you use the Website we will log your IP address, pages you viewed, operating system type, browser type, referring website, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

**Use of Cookies:** We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

### HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We may use the information collected above in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To send you promotional information that you have signed up for previously, such as newsletters. Each email newsletter will provide information on how to easily opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, newsletter confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments if you have selected the subscribe to comments option. Each comment email will provide information on how to unsubscribe or opt-out of future comment subscription emails;
  * To respond to your inquiries submitted through the comment form on the Website;
  * To provide you with adequate user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity;
  * In some instances, to create your account, identify you as a user of the Website, and customize the Website for your account;

### THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

**Google Analytics:** this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may log your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics (i.e., the data is anonymous). 

**Aweber:** this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. Please refer to [Aweber’s privacy policy](https://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm) for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email address or other personal information without your consent. However, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

### ANONYMOUS DATA

Occasionally, we may use anonymous data, which is not able to identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

### PUBLICLY VISIBLE INFORMATION

If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information like your name or website URL may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly, unless you choose to explicitly and voluntarily include it in a comment on the Website. At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website.

You may also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and Google Account.

Users may see your user name, avatar, profile description and website information.

### COOKIES

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record visitor-specific information on what pages users visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner advertisements, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies by the Website by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser that will thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

### ADVERTISING

**Display Ads:** We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements and content when you visit the Website. These may use cookies, as noted above.

**Retargeting Ads:** From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the Website.

**Affiliate Program Participation**

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding affiliate tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of calculating commissions for the Website.

Uncornered Market is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for websites to earn commissions and advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

Uncornered Market is also a participant in the affiliate programs run by Commission Junction, AvantLink, and Flex Offers, as well as other third party direct affiliate programs. These all are affiliate advertising programs designed to provide a means for websites to earn commissions and advertising fees by advertising and links through and to the corresponding affiliate programs. As part of these programs, the Website will post customized links, provided by the appropriate affiliate programs, to track the referrals to their websites and/or to their corresponding partner or client websites. These programs utilize cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

**Newsletters**

You may subscribe to our newsletter via the Website, which may be used for informational and advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows the analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. With these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. The data associated with this tracked behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

### RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

**Opt-out:** You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at info@uncorneredmarket.com if you would like to be removed from our newsletter mailing list.

**Access:** You may request access to the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to info@uncorneredmarket.com.

**Amend:** You may contact us at info@uncorneredmarket.com to update or amend your personal information.

**Forget:** In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget all your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to info@uncorneredmarket.com.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, to complete certain transactions, or when required by law.

### SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number or personal identification number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, trade union memberships or any other sensitive information. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

### CHILDREN'S INFORMATION

The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at info@uncorneredmarket.com and we will use our best efforts to remove such information from our records.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

Please contact us at info@uncorneredmarket.com for any questions you have related to this Privacy Policy. 

**Last updated:** May 12, 2018.
